const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "1) Who sang the title song for the latest Bond film, No Time to Die?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Adele" },
      { id: 2, text: "Sam Smith" },
      { id: 3, text: "Billie Eilish" },
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "2) Which flies a green, white, and orange (in that order) tricolor flag?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Ireland" },
      { id: 2, text: "Ivory Coast" },
      { id: 3, text: "Italy" },
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "3) What company makes the Xperia model of smartphone?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Samsung" },
      { id: 2, text: "Sony" },
      { id: 3, text: "Nokia" },
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "4) Which city is home to the Stuttgart Gate?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Vienna" },
      { id: 2, text: "Zurich" },
      { id: 3, text: "Berlin" },
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "5) Which of the following is NOT a fruit?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Rhubarb" },
      { id: 2, text: "Tomatoes" },
      { id: 3, text: "Avocados" },
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "6) Where was the first example of paper money used?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "China" },
      { id: 2, text: "Turkey" },
      { id: 3, text: "Greece" },
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "7) Who is generally considered the inventor of the motor car?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Henry Ford" },
      { id: 2, text: "Karl Benz" },
      { id: 3, text: "Henry M. Leland" },
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "8) If you were looking at Iguazu Falls, on what continent would you be?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Asia" },
      { id: 2, text: "Africa" },
      { id: 3, text: "South America" },
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "9) What number was the Apollo mission that successfully put a man on the moon for the first time in human history?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Apollo 11" },
      { id: 2, text: "Apollo 12" },
      { id: 3, text: "Apollo 13" },
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "10) Which of the following languages has the longest alphabet?",
    options: [
      { id: 1, text: "Greek" },
      { id: 2, text: "Arabic" },
      { id: 3, text: "Russian" },
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
];

export default questions;
